<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Illini on Matthew Keelan</title>
    <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/tags/illini/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Illini on Matthew Keelan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/illini/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Rose Bowl Trip</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2008/01/rose-bowl-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 01:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2008/01/rose-bowl-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently got the chance to go to Pasadena, CA to watch the Fighting Illini play in the Rose Bowl. The trip was a lot of fun, despite the outcome of the game. I will be posting some pictures shortly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chief</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2007/02/chief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2007/02/chief/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Last performance of Chief Illiniwek was tonight. It&amp;#8217;s a very sad day. An 81 year tradition has been abandoned because of the mis-guided self-righteousness of a few. It&amp;#8217;s sad to see such a great and honorable tradition cast aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am convinced that those who speak out against it, have either never seen it, or had their minds made up against it before they did. I watched it tonight at Joes Bar in Chicago with many other Illinois fans. It perplexes me how anyone could see the emotion, spirit, and respect in Assembly Hall tonight, and every time the Chief performed there and at Memorial Stadium, and describe this tradition as &amp;#8220;hostile and abusive&amp;#8221;. No one will be crying in the stands when the Washington Redskins are re-named. This tradition was truly different, and meant much more to so many people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tradition of Honor, Dignity, and Respect. As an alum of the Marching Illini, I am proud to have been a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the &lt;a href=&#34;http://fightingillini.cstv.com/genrel/022107aaa.html&#34; title=&#34;fightingillini.com&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt; here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;End of an era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodnight&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
