<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Matthew Keelan</title>
    <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/categories/music/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Matthew Keelan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Earthless / Destruction Unit / Yakuza / Running</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2014/01/earthless-destruction-unit-yakuza-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 05:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2014/01/earthless-destruction-unit-yakuza-running/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This show at the Empty Bottle was phenomenal.   All four of these bands put on great shows, and the Bottle is such a great venue.  It had some weird sponsorship thing with Red Bull, so you had to RSVP to get in for $5, but it was first-come first-serve, no guaranteed ticket.  So we got there a little before 9, and the first band didn&amp;#8217;t start until 9:45.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running was first, and I&amp;#8217;m glad I got there to see them.  They had a kind of psych-punk-rock vibe, with echo-y difficult to decipher vocals. Very energetic. They&amp;#8217;re from Chicago, so I&amp;#8217;ll have to make sure to check them out again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yakuza came next, and put on a good set as always.  Noise-y metal with saxophone flourishes from singer/saxophonist Bruce Lamont.  Good stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had never seen Destruction Unit before, nor listened to any of their stuff before the show.  I was blown away.  They played a great, spacey, punky, jammy psyche-rock set, tons of energy, going nuts on stage.  This is a band meant to be seen live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earthless closed out the night.  This was the band I was most excited to see, and they lived up to expectations, and the exceptional bill of this concert.  Instrumental Hendrix-style riffs, with guitar chops to back it up.  These long slow-burn jams to stand back and let the music wash over you.  Really good stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class=&#34;lastfm_widget&#34;&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Hecker / Oneohtrix Point Never</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2014/01/tim-hecker-oneohtrix-point-never/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2014/01/tim-hecker-oneohtrix-point-never/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got to see this show at Lincoln Hall, January 16th, 2014 as part of the Tomorrow Never Knows festival. I was unsure what to expect from this show as both these bands albums are kind of ambient electronic music. I&amp;#8217;ve liked both of these albums a lot. I often listen to them through headphones at work. It&amp;#8217;s a nice backdrop for getting work done, but there&amp;#8217;s also interesting stuff going on in there if you want to listen intently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Hecker was first. He came out to no real fanfare, and went to work on a dark stage, obscurred by a smoke machine. I&amp;#8217;m not sure of what all the equipment he had on stage was. It looked like he was constantly tweaking things. There was a lot going on sonically. Visually, it was difficult to see what was going on. The crowd was standing almost perfectly still, just listening, and drinking their beer. I think some visual component would have added to the show. Personally I would like to see what he was doing up there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oneohtrix Point Never closed the show. They had a screen showing trippy CG animations, as well as logos from old video games. I saw Zork go by up there. They put on a pretty good set. It was 2 guys with laptops up there. It didn&amp;#8217;t seem like as much equipment as Tim Hecker had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I thought this was an interesting show, two acts playing music I don&amp;#8217;t usually see live. It&amp;#8217;s not at the top of my list to see again, but was enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/05/avocado/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2006 07:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/05/avocado/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pearl Jam&amp;#8217;s new album is officially released, Tuesday May 2nd. I received my pre-ordered copy Friday. Thanks, Ten Club.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s a really good album. Upon first listen I thought Riot Act was a much better ablum, and wasn&amp;#8217;t sure why this one was so over-hyped. Riot Act IS a great ablum, which doesn&amp;#8217;t get the respect it deserves, but this self-titled album is really good too. It is growing on me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn&amp;#8217;t sure about &amp;#8220;Marker in the Sand&amp;#8221; at first, but now I think it&amp;#8217;s my favorite song on the album. &amp;#8220;Come Back&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;Gone&amp;#8221;, and &amp;#8220;Inside Job&amp;#8221; are all great songs. &amp;#8220;Life Wasted&amp;#8221; is my favorite of the heavier rock stuff, and the reprise is cool too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially I thought the album kinda lulled in the middle, but &amp;#8220;Marker In The Sand&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;Unemployable&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;Gone&amp;#8221; are all great. &amp;#8220;Big Wave&amp;#8221; is my least favorite song on this release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m still not sure what&amp;#8217;s with all the hype, about this being their &amp;#8220;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rollingstone.com/reviews/album/_/id/9964953/rid/10028282/&#34;&gt;best album in ten years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8220;, or &amp;#8220;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000ETQRCM/ref=ase_matthewkeelan-20/102-2969308-2354536?s=music&amp;amp;v=glance&amp;amp;n=5174&amp;amp;tagActionCode=matthewkeelan-20&#34; title=&#34;eminence - A position of great distinction or superiority&#34;&gt;return to eminence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8221; (This guy also says it&amp;#8217;s their first studio release since 2000, so he doesn&amp;#8217;t even count Riot Act). To me it sounds pretty much like Pearl Jam has since Matt Cameron joined (although &amp;#8216;Binaural&amp;#8217; sounded much better live than in album form, to me at least). It&amp;#8217;s not amazingly better than &amp;#8216;Riot Act&amp;#8217;, not at all, and it doesn&amp;#8217;t sound like Vs. or Ten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all it&amp;#8217;s a good album, from a band that has continuously put out good albums. I can&amp;#8217;t wait to see them perform these songs live in a couple weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
