<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Matthew Keelan</title>
    <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/tags/linux/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Matthew Keelan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux&#43; Study Guide pdf version is Windows-Only</title>
      <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/linux-plus-study-guide-pdf-windows-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2006 12:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/linux-plus-study-guide-pdf-windows-only/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently purchased a Linux+ Study Guide. The Linux+ Study Guide Third Edition by author Roderick W. Smith, published by Sybex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far the book is pretty good, i am almost finished with it. I haven&amp;#8217;t taken the exam yet, so i can&amp;#8217;t yet say how well it has prepared me. [I recently purchased a Linux+ Study Guide. The Linux+ Study Guide Third Edition by author Roderick W. Smith, published by Sybex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far the book is pretty good, i am almost finished with it. I haven&amp;#8217;t taken the exam yet, so i can&amp;#8217;t yet say how well it has prepared me.]&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/078214389X/matthewkeelan-20&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; However, I cannot recommend buying this book, or any book published by Sybex, if you like to read the pdf version. This book came with a cd that includes a pdf edition of the book. This pdf, however is useless on linux. Another lousy DRM scheme that hurts paying customers who want to read the pdf file for which they paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Support FAQ on their website indicates that they have been &lt;a href=&#34;http://wiley.custhelp.com/cgi-bin/wiley.cfg/php/enduser/std_adp.php?p_faqid=2862&#34;&gt;&amp;#8220;working to correct this&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt; for some time now. I contacted support, and they appologized, but could not provide me with a usable version of the pdf file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back cover of the book lists the items featured on the cd:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Test Engine, which they indicate works on both windows and linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Electronic Flashcards, which they indicate can run off your PC, Pocket PC, or Palm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Entire book in searchable and printable pdf, with no indication that it is useless in Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one would have any reason to believe a pdf file would be Windows-Only, and the fact that this is a Linux book makes this incredibly stupid. For this reason, even though it seems to be a decent book, I cannot recommend this, or any book published by Sybex, to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
