<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on Matthew Keelan</title>
    <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/categories/sports/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on Matthew Keelan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Rose Bowl Trip</title>
      <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2008/01/rose-bowl-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 01:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2008/01/rose-bowl-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently got the chance to go to Pasadena, CA to watch the Fighting Illini play in the Rose Bowl. The trip was a lot of fun, despite the outcome of the game. I will be posting some pictures shortly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chief</title>
      <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2007/02/chief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2007 05:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2007/02/chief/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Last performance of Chief Illiniwek was tonight. It&amp;#8217;s a very sad day. An 81 year tradition has been abandoned because of the mis-guided self-righteousness of a few. It&amp;#8217;s sad to see such a great and honorable tradition cast aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am convinced that those who speak out against it, have either never seen it, or had their minds made up against it before they did. I watched it tonight at Joes Bar in Chicago with many other Illinois fans. It perplexes me how anyone could see the emotion, spirit, and respect in Assembly Hall tonight, and every time the Chief performed there and at Memorial Stadium, and describe this tradition as &amp;#8220;hostile and abusive&amp;#8221;. No one will be crying in the stands when the Washington Redskins are re-named. This tradition was truly different, and meant much more to so many people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tradition of Honor, Dignity, and Respect. As an alum of the Marching Illini, I am proud to have been a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the &lt;a href=&#34;http://fightingillini.cstv.com/genrel/022107aaa.html&#34; title=&#34;fightingillini.com&#34;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt; here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;End of an era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodnight&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frank Thomas</title>
      <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/frank-thomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2006 09:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/frank-thomas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think Frank Thomas and Ken Williams &lt;a href=&#34;http://sports.espn.go.com/mlb/news/story?id=2309202&#34; title=&#34;Thomas disses Sox&#34;&gt;both&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://chicagosports.chicagotribune.com/sports/baseball/whitesox/cs-0602270182feb27,1,862317.story?coll=cs-baseball-print&#34; title=&#34;Williams - &#39;He&#39;s an Idiot&#39;&#34;&gt;talk&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://sports.espn.go.com/espn/wire?section=mlb&amp;amp;id=2345960&#34; title=&#34;Williams Angry&#34;&gt;too&lt;/a&gt; much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will say that I would rather this happen now, than at the end of last season. It could have distracted from the great season the White Sox brought us last year. Dispite whatever Frank wants to say now, as a long-time fan, I&amp;#8217;m glad he was a part of the 2005 White Sox, I&amp;#8217;m glad I got to see him throw out the first pitch of the playoffs, and I&amp;#8217;m glad I was able to see him hold up the World Series Trophy at the rally, after the parade. Those moments will be remembered for much longer than comments reported in the off-season, and spring training anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will miss Frank Thomas being on the White Sox (especially if he contributes to the Oakland A&amp;#8217;s usual destruction of the Sox), even if Ken Williams doesn&amp;#8217;t. I think Frank deserves a great deal of respect and honor for the career he had here. Ken Williams should have stuck with his original plan that he stated at SoxFest, to not speak publicly about bad-blood that goes on behind the scenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m glad I got to see Frank Thomas hit so many home runs for the White Sox, and become the greatest hitter in franchise history. I think holding a World Series Trophy over his head at an extremely well-attended victory rally is a fitting end to Frank Thomas great White Sox career, even if he doesn&amp;#8217;t.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sox Fest 2006</title>
      <link>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/sox-fest-2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2006 14:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.matthewkeelan.com/2006/02/sox-fest-2006/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I attended SoxFest 2006, with my friends Brad, John J., and Jesse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was cool. We got to hear Ozzie Guillen, Ken Williams, and Hawk talk about the amazing 2005 World Series Championship season, and what is sure to be a great 2006. We also got to see an introduction to Jim Thome, and Rob Mackowiak, as well as new radio voice, and former Sox player, Chris Singleton. Thome should be a good addition if he is healthy next season, and Mackowiak should be a good utility player. Singleton can&amp;#8217;t replace Rooney, who was always excellent, but hopefully he&amp;#8217;ll be ok, at least he&amp;#8217;s not Mike North, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all SoxFest was great, and next season should be too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
