<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Singapore on Matthew Keelan</title>
    <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/tags/singapore/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Singapore on Matthew Keelan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/tags/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Back From Singapore</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/04/back-from-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2006 19:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/04/back-from-singapore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am now back in Chicago. My appologies for not updating much last week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I had to work in Singapore at night. Joe came in friday night and will be working the next two weeks in Singapore, as I am home now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Saturday Joe and I went out to lunch, and to explore Orchard Road. We went to eat at a place called Cafe Cartel, I think. The food was pretty good, the place was kind of strange, they took your order, and immeadiately brought out a receipt, we paid for it, and then they crossed stuff off as it was brought out to us. Joe wondered aloud, what happens if we want more to drink, or are these free refills?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me, to the waiter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;#8220;Can we have more drinks, please?&amp;#8221;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waiter (with the most confused look I have ever seen anyone give, like when someone asks George Bush an unscripted question, times ten)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;#8220;More drinks???&amp;#8221;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;#8220;Yes, two more drinks&amp;#8221;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;#8220;Yeah, we had the Peach Iced Tea, two more of them.&amp;#8221;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waiter (still very confused)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;#8220;You want two more glasses to drink?&amp;#8221;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then he radios to someone, and a receipt is quickly brought out for two glasses of peach iced tea. It would be 30 minutes or so before those drinks would be brought out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you&amp;#8217;re ever eating at a Cafe Cartel restaurant in Singapore, or possibly anywhere, remember that you will only be able to get one drink. A second drink is such an odd request, that it can&amp;#8217; really be handled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday night we all went out the see Ice Age 2, myself. It was pretty good, I hadn&amp;#8217; seen the first one, so don&amp;#8217;t know if it was better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday and Tuesday we went to Sentosa during the day, went on the luge again, rented bikes, and ate lunch there. Monday thunder and lightning started before we had a chance to go swimming, so we went back Tuesday, and went swimming first, then we got caught in the storm while riding around the bike trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday night we went out for one last good dinner, for me. We went to a nice Japanese restaurant, had some sushi, sake, steak, and wasabi ice cream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My trip to Singapore was great. I wouldn&amp;#8217;t mind going back&amp;#8230; &lt;img src=&#34;http://matthewkeelan.com/blog/templates/default/img/emoticons/smile.png&#34; alt=&#34;:-)&#34; style=&#34;display: inline; vertical-align: bottom;&#34; class=&#34;emoticon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentosa</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/sentosa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2006 18:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/sentosa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday we went to Sentosa Island. It&amp;#8217;s a small island off of Singapore, and a theme park type place. We took a cable car over to it, from Harbour Front, where our office is located. It was a pretty cool place. We went up in the Sky Tower, where you could see a pretty good view of the island, the city, and the ocean, as it rotated around. Then we went to the underwater world aquarium, and got to see fish, sharks, stingrays, and giant crabs. The luge was very cool, kind of a go-cart race down a hill, then take a chair lift back up, lots of fun. There was a dolphin show, which was pretty good, although it was extremely hot there, and the dolpin&amp;#8217;s were kind of far away. There was a lot of construction going on too, the park was still under developement. There were a few beaches It was a lot of fun there, and wasn&amp;#8217;t too crowded, although the 7:40 musical fountain show was full, at 7:15, and we had to wait for the 8:40. That was pretty good, cool laser effects, and fountain effects, and a weird cartoon projected onto water. Then we took the cable car back, and went in for a night of work. A long day, but good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 03:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sunday we went to try and find a sushi place called Aoki, but it could not be found. We went to a Chinese place, had a nice meal and some sake. I never had Sake before, it was good, tastes like vodka, but a lot smoother, doesn&amp;#8217;t burn your throat, and isn&amp;#8217;t as strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we went back to the bar with the beer garden, and the cover band, the older guy who sang Elvis songs came back, he&amp;#8217;s entertaining, I asked them to play anything Pearl Jam, and they played Last Kiss. It was good. I had a black cactus &amp;#8211; tequilla, blackberry brandy, and soda water, not a bad drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday we started work. The buiding is nice, not as big as the one in Chicago, but the office is pretty nice. They have a caffeteria with about a hundred different food stands. I had some kind of chicken, and fresh banana juice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday evening we went to a fancy/expensive Indian restaurant. It was excellent, wine, naan bread, chicken, lobster, all excellent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got to chill in the pool for a bit after work, it was quite relaxing, though the pool area was pretty much empty.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Arrival</title>
      <link>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/singapore-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2006 02:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrkeelan.github.io/2006/03/singapore-arrival/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Singapore Saturday evening, after I slept for pretty much the entire flight from London. The airport was very nice, and very clean, out side there were palm trees and flowers, I could tell immeadiately how nice it was here. It was 35 degrees Celsius, about 95 Farenheit, when we arrived. It cooled off as the sun went down. The weather has been very nice, doesn&amp;#8217;t feel too hot. We took a cab to the apartment, cab rides are pretty inexpensive here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The apartment we are staying in is very nice, and there is a lot to do in the surrounding area. We went out for dinner close by, the food here is unbelievably good, everything, very good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walked down Orchard Street, a major street here, lots of shops, coffee shops, and restaurants around, a few bars, and lots and lots of people around. I&amp;#8217;ve been doing a lot more walking here than I had been in Chicago, it&amp;#8217;s been nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week we are working a regular 9am-4pm, or so, Singapore time schedule, it&amp;#8217;s nice to be on a regular schedule, to get off work, go out for dinner, and drinks, and then go to sleep. I realize I have been getting a little sick of the 3rd Shift schedule, after a year of working it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Singapore is really great so far, I&amp;#8217;m very glad to be lucky enough to be here right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://matthewkeelan.com/gallery/Singapore&#34; title=&#34;Singapore Photos&#34;&gt;Photos&lt;/a&gt; &amp;lt;&amp;#8211; More Added&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
